at
Jesus
mocking
The crowd
from
reading
the cross was
script
a
it.
know
didn't
they just
before,
years
A thousand
the
how
recorded
twenty-two
Psalm
be mocked
would
Messiah
gestures,
the
words.
and the
the head,
shake
"...they
saying,
LORD
the
He trusted on
deliver him:
would
that he
him..." At
deliver
let him
cross,
the
it
gospel records
Matthew's
their heads,
wagging
the passers-by
nearly line
sneering
the rulers
line:
for
God;
in
"He trusted
him now,
deliver
let him
him:
have
if he will
said,
for he
the Son of
am
I
they were
They thought
God."
the cruelty.
inventing
prophecy
reciting
They were
that this was
witnesses
unwilling
One.
the
more
one
And they threw
at Him:
taunt
thyself.
"save
be the Son
thou
If
God,
of
cross."
from the
down
come
have
But He could
down.
He was the
showed
He
the
escaping
Son not by
cross,
on it
staying
but by
could
He
scorn
bearing the
silenced,
have
throwing
people
for the very
it.
is
mocked
The man they
the whole song
One
the
about.
was
the King to
told
They
down
come
did.
never
and He
scorn
under
He stayed
theirs,
ours
and
scorners.
to win the
from
reading
And they were
finished:
never
a script they
with all
ends
the song
world
the
the ends of
to Him.
turning
Turn,
One
the
and come to
down.
come
who would not